How to make a backlight strip in Clover?
First, add a name line to the place where the backlight strip needs to be added.
Then modify the name line type to text.
Here you can see the name line text.
Next, make a backlight strip text in PS.
The size of the text is set to 100x200 pixels.
The resolution is 300.
You can find some pictures with texture.
Or you can directly scan the material as a texture.
Process the interface of the texture.
After processing, let's save it.
After saving, we will add the texture of the backlight strip.
Add it to the name line texture.
Then set the strength of the backlight strip.
Set it to 20.
Use it to create a backlight strip.
Next, set the material to metal.
Then adjust the roughness of the surface.
Set it to 40.
The strength of the backlight is 100.
The metal density is set to 80.
Adjust the thickness of the name line.
Set it to 5mm.
Then set the thickness of the line.
Set it to 1cm.
This is the width of the backlight strip you need.
Next, I will explain how to add backlight strips to the curve.
Use the free name line to add a whole circle of name lines.
You can see that if you use the name line setting just now,
the position of the backlight strip and the thickness are incompatible.
So copy a name line in the canvas window.
Change this name line to the original name line.
Then open the attribute editor.
In the attribute editor, adjust the gap of the name line to 1.5mm.
Adjust the length of the line to 1mm.
Adjust the thickness of the line to 0.30mm.
Adjust the thickness of the line to 3mm.
Such a position and size,
such a position and size,
The position and size are matching for the curve line.
But the effect now, the texture of the line has a lot of creases.
So you need to use the edit line tool.
Select this line.
Open the curve and smooth in the attribute editor.
You can see that the backlight strip is now smooth.
And there are no creases.
Click to turn over, you can turn over the direction of the backlight strip.
There is a small creases at the end of the line.
In this case, you need to add another line to cover the creases.
You also need to turn it over.
And you can see that the whole edge is smooth.
Now, you can add a new line to the curve.
In this case, you need to add another line to the curve.
Click to turn over.
And there you have it.
Now, we are going to create a new line.
And click on the next line.
And we add another line to the curve.
You can see the line is now smooth.
Now, click to turn over.
And you can see the line is smooth.